Register of the Guy Jean Pauker Papers, 1928-1996
Hoover Institution Archives
- INDONESIA SUBJECT FILE, 1945-1980. (Box 6-62)
  - Suryohadiprojo, Sayidiman, National Resilience: In Indonesian Approach to Peace and Prosperity, n.d. (Folder 2)
  - Tektjeng, Lie
    - An Indonesian View: The Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution, Djakarta, 1970 (Folder 3)
    - Some Remarks on Modern China Studies: The Great Proletarian Cultural Revolution As Seen From Djakarta, Djakarta, 1971 (Folder 4)
    - Tentang Arti Strategis Perundingan Paris: Suatu Analisa, Djakarta, 1970 (Folder 5)
  - Tektjeng, Lie and Yoshida Teigo, Some Remarks on the Problems and Difficulties Besetting Present-Day Indonesian-Japanese Relations, Djakarta, 1970 (Folder 6)
  - Thajeb, Sjarif
    - General (Folder 7)
    - Speech, Indonesian-American Chamber of Commerce, January 13, 1972 (Folder 8)
  - TKR, PPK, gang activities, 1953-57 (Folder 9)
  - United States of America
    - Department of State, Indonesia Facts Book, May 1970 (Folder 10)
    - Exhibit and the 1955 Djakarta Fair (Folder 11)
    - Government
      - Agreement concerning civil uses of atomic energy, May 1971 (Folder 12)
      - Telephone directory, Djakarta, 1962 (Folder 13)
    - Mission in Indonesia, telephone and personnel directories
      - July 1970 (Folder 14)
      - July 1971 (Folder 15)
  - Van Niel, Robert, Indonesian Political Developments, Far Eastern Survey, Vol. XXII, No. 7, June 1953 (Folder 16)
  - Wertheim, W. F., The Sociological Approach to Indonesian Historiography, June 1959 (Folder 17)
  - West Irian (Folder 18-19)
- INDONESIAN LANGUAGE MATERIALS
  - Indonesian Language Materials (Box 63-68., Box 63-69)
  - Indonesian Language Materials (Box 69., Folder 1-2)
- U.S. DEPARTMENT OF THE INTERIOR. OFFICE OF INDIAN AFFAIRS. NAVAJO SERVICE. 1942-1950. (Box 69-72)
  Minutes of meetings, proceedings, resolutions and correspondence, pertaining to Navajo tribal affairs.
  - General (Box 69., Folder 3)
  - Navajo Tribal Council
    - Advisory Committee, Proceedings of Meetings
      - 1949
        - March 4-7 (Folder 4)
        - April 4-6 (Folder 5)
        - July 6-9 (Box 70., Folder 1)
      - 1950
        - January 24 - February 2 (Folder 2)
        - May 16-18 (Folder 3)
    - Advisory Committee and Industrial Committee, Proceedings of Meeting with the Traders' Association, March 31 - April 2, 1948 (Folder 4)
    - Minutes
      - 1943
        - July 9-11 (Folder 5)
        - November 26-27 (Folder 6)
      - 1944, July 17-19 (Folder 7)
      - 1945
        - July 10-13 (Folder 8)
        - December 18-20 (Folder 9)
    - Proceedings of Meetings
      - 1942, January 12-13 (Folder 10)
      - 1946, July 23-26 (Folder 11)
      - 1947, February 18-21 (Box 71., Folder 1)
      - 1948
        - March 18-23 (Folder 2)
        - June 26, 28, 29 (Folder 3)
        - December 6-9 (Folder 4)
      - 1949
        - June 8-11 (Folder 5)
        - October 11-14 (Folder 6)
      - 1950
        - March 1, 15, 16 (Folder 7)
        - April 11-14 (Box 72., Folder 1)
        - June 26 (Folder 2)
        - July 10-13 (Folder 3)
        - September 11-15 (Folder 4)
    - Proceedings of the Grazing Meeting, September 13-14, 1949 (Folder 5)
    - Resolutions for presentations to the Navajo Tribal Council, December 17, 1945 (Folder 6)
- TRIALS OF PARTICIPANTS IN THE INDONESIAN 30 SEPTEMBER 1965 COUP, 1966-68 (Box 72-98)
  Photocopies of hearings, verdicts and other court issued documentation pertaining to the activities of the coup participants and the Indonesian court decisions and sentences.
  - Amar Hanafia/A.G. Gani Trials I and II (Box 73., Folder 1-2)
  - Dani, Omar
    - Trial I (Box 74., Folder 1)
    - Trial II (Folder 2)
    - Trial III (Box 75., Folder 1)
  - Hidajat, Tamuri, trial (Box 76., Folder 1)
  - Moeljono, Major, trial (Box 77., Folder 1)
  - Muljono (Walujo)
    - Trial I (Folder 2)
    - Trial II (Box 78., Folder 1)
  - Nasution, Djalaludin Jusuf
    - File (Box 79., Folder 1)
    - Trial (Folder 2)
  - Nazir, Moh. and Lt. Col. Maliki trials (Box 80., Folder 1)
  - Ngadimo trial (Folder 2)
  - Pardede, Peris
    - File (Box 81., Folder 1)
    - Trial (Folder 2)
  - Njono file (Box 82., Folder 1)
  - Rabidi, Joseph, trial (Folder 2)
  - Ramelan, Utomo
    - Trial I (Box 83., Folder 1)
    - Trial II (Box 84., Folder 1)
  - Rivai, Djohan, trial (Box 85., Folder 1)
  - Sjam
    - File I (Folder 2)
    - File II (Box 86., Folder 1)
    - File III (Folder 2)
    - Verdict (Box 87., Folder 1)
  - Subandrio
    - Trial I (Folder 2)
    - Trial II (Box 88., Folder 1)
  - Sudisman
    - File I (Box 89., Folder 1)
    - Trial I (Folder 2)
    - File II (Box 90., Folder 1)
    - Trial II (Box 91., Folder 1)
  - Sujono, Major, trial (Folder 2)
  - Sukrisno, Gatot, trial (Box 92., Folder 1)
  - Supardjo
    - File (Folder 2)
    - Trial I (Box 93., Folder 1)
    - Trial II (Folder 2)
  - Suwardiningsih trial (Box 94., Folder 1)
  - Ulung Sitepu/Maniso trial (Box 95., Folder 1)
  - Untung's sentence (Folder 2)
  - Wirjomartono
    - File (Folder 3)
    - Trial (Box 96., Folder 1)
    - Requisitor and verdict (Folder 2)
  - Wirjoatmodjo/Sugeng Sugiarto
    - File (Box 96A., Folder 1)
    - Trial (Box 97., Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 98., Folder 1)
- U.S. EMBASSY, DJAKARTA, 1958-1979 (Box 99-133)
  News bulletins, editorials, excerpts, summaries and translations from the Indonesian press issued by the U.S. Embassy in Djakarta.
  - Daily press summaries
    - December 1970 (Box 99., Folder 1)
    - 1971
      - January-June (Folder 2)
      - July-September (Folder 3)
      - October-December (Folder 4)
    - 1972
      - January-March (Folder 5)
      - April-May (Folder 6)
      - August-October (Folder 7)
      - November-December (Folder 8)
    - 1973
      - January-March (Folder 9)
      - April-June (Folder 10)
      - July-September (Box 100., Folder 1)
      - October-December (Folder 2)
    - 1974
      - January-March (Folder 3)
      - April-June (Folder 4)
      - July-September (Folder 5)
      - October-December (Folder 6)
    - 1975
      - January-March (Folder 7)
      - April-June (Folder 8)
      - July-September (Folder 9)
      - October-December (Box 101., Folder 1)
    - 1976
      - January-February (Folder 2)
      - March-June (Folder 3)
      - July-August (Folder 4)
      - September-December (Folder 5)
    - 1977
      - January-April (Folder 6)
      - May-July (Folder 7)
      - August-October (Folder 8)
      - November-December (Folder 9)
    - 1978
      - January-February (Folder 10)
      - March-April (Box 102., Folder 1)
      - May-August (Folder 2)
      - September-December (Folder 3)
    - January-April 1979 (Folder 4)
  - Djakarta press summaries
    - 1960
      - January (Folder 5)
      - February (Folder 6)
      - March (Folder 7)
      - April (Folder 8)
      - May (Box 103., Folder 1-2)
      - June (Folder 3-4)
      - July (Folder 5)
      - August-September (Folder 6)
      - October-November (Box 104., Folder 1)
      - December (Folder 2)
    - 1961
      - January (Folder 3)
      - February (Folder 4)
      - May-June (Folder 5)
      - June-July (Folder 6)
      - August (Folder 7)
      - September (Box 105., Folder 1)
      - September-October (Folder 2)
      - October (Folder 3)
      - November (Folder 4)
      - December (Folder 5)
    - 1962
      - January (Folder 6)
      - February (Box 106., Folder 1)
      - March (Folder 2)
      - April (Folder 3)
      - April-May (Folder 4)
      - June (Folder 5)
      - June-July (Folder 6)
      - July (Folder 7)
      - August (Box 107., Folder 1)
      - September (Folder 2)
      - October (Folder 3)
      - November (Folder 4)
      - December (Folder 5)
    - 1963
      - January (Folder 6)
      - February (Folder 7)
      - March (Folder 8)
      - April (Box 108., Folder 1)
      - May (Folder 2)
      - June (Folder 3)
      - July (Folder 4)
      - August (Folder 5)
      - September (Folder 6)
      - October (Folder 7)
      - November (Folder 8)
      - December (Box 109., Folder 1)
    - 1964
      - Janaury-February (Folder 2)
      - March (Folder 3)
      - April (Folder 4)
      - May (Folder 5)
      - June (Folder 6)
      - July-August (Folder 7)
      - September (Folder 8)
      - October (Box 110., Folder 1)
      - November-December (Folder 2)
    - January-March 1965 (Folder 3)
    - June-December 1964 (Folder 4)
  - Indonesian press editorials
    - 1958
      - January (Folder 5)
      - February (Folder 6)
      - February-March (Folder 7)
      - March-April (Folder 8)
      - April (Box 111., Folder 1)
      - May (Folder 2)
      - June (Folder 3)
      - July (Folder 4)
      - August (Folder 5)
      - September (Folder 6)
      - October (Folder 7)
      - November (Box 112., Folder 1)
      - December (Folder 2)
    - 1959
      - January (Folder 3)
      - February (Folder 4)
      - March (Folder 5)
      - April (Folder 6)
      - May (Folder 7)
      - June (Box 113., Folder 1)
      - July (Folder 2)
      - August (Folder 3)
      - September (Folder 4)
      - October (Folder 5)
      - November (Folder 6)
      - December (Folder 7)
  - Medan press summaries
    - August-December 1961 (Box 114., Folder 1)
    - 1962
      - January-June (Folder 2)
      - July-September (Folder 3)
      - October-December (Folder 4)
    - 1963
      - January-May (Folder 5)
      - June-December (Folder 6)
    - 1964
      - January-August (Folder 7)
      - September-December (Box 115., Folder 1)
    - 1965
      - January-February (Folder 2)
  - News bulletin, November 10, 1966 (Folder 3)
  - Surabaya press summaries
    - September-December 1961 (Folder 4)
    - 1962
      - January-February (Folder 5)
      - October-December (Folder 6)
    - 1963
      - January-May (Folder 7)
      - June-November (Folder 8)
    - 1964
      - May-October (Folder 9)
      - November-December (Box 116., Folder 1)
    - 1965
      - January-August (Folder 2)
      - September-October (Folder 3)
      - November-December (Folder 4)
    - January-December 1966 (Folder 5)
    - January 1967 (Folder 6)
  - Translation Unit press reviews
    - 1965
      - September (Folder 7)
      - October (Folder 8)
      - November (Folder 9)
      - December (Box 117., Folder 1)
    - 1966
      - January (Folder 2)
      - February (Folder 3)
      - March (Folder 4)
      - April (Folder 5)
      - May (Folder 6)
      - June (Folder 7)
      - July (Folder 8)
      - August (Box 118., Folder 1)
      - September (Folder 2)
      - October (Folder 3)
      - November (Folder 4)
      - December (Folder 5)
    - 1967
      - January (Folder 6)
      - February (Folder 7)
      - February-March (Box 119., Folder 1)
      - April (Folder 2)
      - April-May (Folder 3)
      - May (Folder 4)
      - June (Folder 5-6)
      - July (Folder 7)
      - July-August (Box 120., Folder 1)
      - August (Folder 2)
      - September (Folder 3)
      - October (Folder 4)
      - November (Folder 5)
      - December (Folder 6)
    - 1968
      - January (Folder 7)
      - February (Box 121., Folder 1)
      - March (Folder 2)
      - April (Folder 3)
      - May (Folder 3A)
      - June (Folder 4)
      - July (Folder 5)
      - August (Folder 6)
      - September (Folder 7)
      - October (Box 122., Folder 1)
      - November (Folder 2)
      - December (Folder 3)
    - 1969
      - January (Folder 4)
      - February (Folder 5)
      - March (Folder 6)
      - April (Folder 7)
      - May (Folder 8)
      - June (Folder 9)
      - July (Folder 10)
      - August (Box 123., Folder 1)
      - September (Folder 2)
      - October (Folder 3)
      - November (Folder 4)
      - December (Folder 5)
    - 1970
      - January (Folder 6)
      - February (Folder 7)
      - March (Folder 8)
      - April (Box 124., Folder 1)
      - May (Folder 2)
      - June (Folder 3)
      - July (Folder 4)
      - August (Folder 5)
      - September (Folder 6)
      - October (Folder 7)
      - November (Folder 8)
      - December (Folder 9)
    - 1971
      - January (Folder 10)
      - February (Folder 11)
      - March (Box 125., Folder 1)
      - April (Folder 2)
      - May (Folder 3)
      - June (Folder 4)
      - July (Folder 5)
      - August (Folder 6)
      - September (Folder 7)
      - October (Folder 8)
      - November (Folder 9)
      - December (Folder 10)
    - 1972
      - January (Folder 11)
      - February (Box 126., Folder 1)
      - March (Folder 2)
      - April (Folder 3)
      - May (Folder 4)
      - June (Folder 5)
      - July (Folder 6)
      - August (Folder 7)
      - September (Folder 8)
      - October (Box 127., Folder 1)
      - November (Folder 2)
      - December (Folder 3)
    - 1973
      - January (Folder 4)
      - February (Folder 5)
      - March (Folder 6)
      - April (Folder 7)
      - May (Folder 8)
      - June (Folder 9)
      - July (Box 128., Folder 1)
      - August (Folder 2)
      - September (Folder 3)
      - October (Folder 4)
      - November (Folder 5)
      - December (Folder 6)
    - 1974
      - January (Folder 7)
      - February (Folder 8)
      - March (Folder 9)
      - April (Folder 10)
      - May (Box 129., Folder 1)
      - June (Folder 2)
      - July (Folder 3)
      - August (Folder 4)
      - September (Folder 5)
      - October (Folder 6)
      - November-December (Folder 7)
    - 1975
      - January (Folder 8)
      - February (Folder 9)
      - March (Folder 10)
      - April (Box 130., Folder 1)
      - May (Folder 2)
      - June (Folder 3)
      - July (Folder 4)
      - August (Folder 5)
      - September (Folder 6)
      - October (Folder 7)
      - November (Folder 8)
      - December (Folder 9)
    - 1976
      - January (Folder 10)
      - February (Folder 11)
      - March (Folder 12)
      - April-May (Box 131., Folder 1)
      - June (Folder 2)
      - July (Folder 3)
      - September (Folder 4)
      - October (Folder 5)
      - November (Folder 6)
    - 1977
      - January (Folder 7)
      - February (Folder 8)
      - March (Folder 9)
      - April (Folder 10)
      - May (Folder 11)
      - June (Folder 12)
      - July (Box 132., Folder 1)
      - August (Folder 2)
      - September (Folder 3)
      - October (Folder 4)
      - November (Folder 5)
      - December (Folder 6)
    - 1978
      - January (Folder 7)
      - February (Folder 8)
      - March (Folder 9)
      - April (Folder 10)
      - May (Folder 11)
      - June-July (Box 133., Folder 1)
      - August-September (Folder 2)
      - October-November (Folder 3)
      - December (Folder 4)
    - 1979
      - January (Folder 5)
      - February (Folder 6)
      - March (Folder 7)
      - April (Folder 8)
- SUBJECT FILE, 1952-1974 (Box 133-141)
  Correspondence, essays, reports, speeches, studies, printed matter, and other materials pertaining to G. Pauker's research and writing activities.
  - Abdurrachman, H. (Box 133., Folder 9)
  - Afro-Asian Journalists Conference, Djakarta, April 26, 1963, Malayan Delegation, speech by leader of (Folder 10)
  - Agassi, Judith B., Mass Media in Indonesia, Cambridge, Massachusetts, December 1969 (Box 134., Folder 1)
  - Armed forces in underdeveloped countries, 1959 (Folder 2)
  - The Asia Foundation (Folder 3)
  - Asia Society, Washington Center, luncheon, May 9, 1973 (Folder 4)
  - Asian Development Bank, Philippines, press release, 1974 (Folder 5)
  - Asian-African Conference, Bandung, April 1955
    - General (Folder 6)
    - African National Congress and the South African Indian Congress, press statement by representatives of, April 17, 1955 (Folder 7)
    - Ali, Moh., Prime Minister of Pakistan, speech, April 9, 1955 (Folder 8)
    - Asian-African Conference Bulletin (Folder 9)
    - Botsio, Minister of State, Gold Coast Government, address by, April 1955 (Folder 10)
    - Chou En-Lai
      - Speech, April 19, 1955 (Folder 11)
      - Speech, April 24, 1955 (Folder 12)
      - Supplementary speech, April 19, 1955 (Folder 13)
    - Clippings (Folder 14)
    - Committee On Cultural Cooperation (Folder 15)
    - Culture and Information, a working paper from the government of the Republic of Indonesia (Folder 16)
    - Directory, 2nd edition (Folder 17)
    - Draft final communiques (Folder 18-19)
    - Economic Committee (Folder 20)
    - Economic Cooperation, background paper prepared by the Joint Secretariat (Folder 21)
    - El-Azem, Khaled, Minister of Foreign Affairs of Syria and Chairman of Syrian Delegation, speech, n.d. (Folder 22)
    - Ethiopian Delegation, address by the Chairman of, April 19, 1955 (Folder 23)
    - Grand Mufti of Palestine, statement by, April 23 (Folder 24)
    - Guide to the members of the conference (Folder 25)
    - Information handbook (Folder 26)
    - Jamali, Mohammad Fadhill, speech by (Folder 27)
    - Japanese Delegation, address by Tatsunosuke Takasi (Folder 28)
    - Kalmuck Brotherhood (Folder 29)
    - Kotelawala, Sir John, Prime Minister of Ceylon, address by at the opening session of the conference, April 18 (Folder 30)
    - Labour Front and Peoples' Action Party of Singapore, joint statement issued by representatives of, April 23 (Folder 31)
    - Liberian Delegation statements
      - April 19 (Folder 32)
      - April 18 (Box 135., Folder 1)
    - Naim, Sardar Mohammad, Head of Afghan Delegation, statement (Folder 2)
    - Nasar, Rusi, former officer of the Turkistani Legion, To the President of the Asian-African Conference (Folder 3)
    - Naser, Gamal, Prime Minister of Egypt, statement, April 18 (Folder 4)
    - Nehru, Pandit, conversation with and footnote by Chou En-Lai, April 25 (Folder 5)
    - News Bulletin (Folder 6-7)
    - Peoples' Action Party of Malaya, press statment issued by, April 17 (Folder 8)
    - Pham Van Dong, Vietnam Delegation, statements
      - April 22 (Folder 9)
      - April 24 (Folder 10)
    - Press announcements and communiques (Folder 11)
    - Press Subcommittee (Folder 12)
    - Romulo, Carlos P., Chairman of the Philippine Delegation, opening statement, n.d. (Folder 13)
    - Sastroamidjojo, Ali
      - Address by, n.d. (Folder 14)
      - Closing speech, n.d. (Folder 15)
    - Sihanouk, Norodom, Head of the Cambodian Delegation, statement by (Folder 16)
    - Solh, Sami, Prime Minister of Lebanon, statement delivered by, April 19 (Folder 17)
    - Speeches and communiques (Folder 18)
    - Sukarno, Achmed
      - Let a New Asia and New Africa Be Born!, speech at the opening of the conference, April 18 (Folder 19)
      - Message through Radio Cairo, April 19 (Folder 20)
    - Thailand representative, address by (Folder 21)
    - Turkey delegate, speech by, April 19 (Folder 22)
    - Yeman Delegation (Folder 23)
    - Youssef, Sala Ben, Head of the Tunisian Delegation, declaration by, April 24 (Folder 24)
  - Asian Socialist Conference, Rangoon, Burma, 1952-53 (Folder 25)
  - Benda, Harry J., Reflections On Asian Communism, reprint, The Yale Review, Vol. LVI, No. 1, October 1966 (Folder 26)
  - Books, official publications, orders, invoices, lists (Folder 27)
  - Brackman, Arnold G., Maphilindo: A Chinese Barrier?, n.d. (Folder 28)
  - Brockway, Fenner
    - Malaysia: A Challenge to Neutralism, article, London Tribune, September 24, 1963 (Box 136., Folder 1)
    - Report on Malaysia, 1963 (Folder 2)
  - Budiardjo, Sukesi (Folder 3)
  - Bundy, McGeorge, remarks, American Association for the Advancement of Science, Philadelphia, December 27, 1962 (Folder 4)
  - Communist objectives in Africa and Asia, 1961 (Folder 5)
  - Conference on Indonesian Studies, Madison, Wisconsin, July 26-29, 1973 (Folder 6)
  - Cowan, C. D., The Political Evolution of South and Southeast Asia Since Independence,' n.d. (Folder 7)
  - Doyle, Leonard, Reducing the Barriers to Private Foreign Investment in Underdeveloped Countries, article, California Management Review, Vol. I, No. 1, Fall 1958 (Folder 8)
  - Emerson, Rupert, The Atlantic Community and the Emerging Countries, reprint, International Organization, Vol. XVII, No. 3, 1963 (Folder 9)
  - Gailbraith, Francis J., Fourth of July Message, Djakarta, July 4, 1965 (Folder 10)
  - Geertz, Clifford, Ethos, World-View and the Analysis of Sacred Symbols, reprint, The Antioch Review, Winter 1957-58 (Folder 11)
  - Green, Marshall, Communist China As a Problem in U.S. Policy Making, Princeton University, February 26, 1965 (Folder 12)
  - Hadi, Asmara, Nine Thesis of Marhaenism and Brief Explanations of Them, October 1960 (Folder 13)
  - Halpern, A.M., The Emergence of An Asian Communist Coalition, reprint, The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, Vol. 349, September 1963 (Folder 14)
  - Harono, Major General, Towards Stalibity in Indonesia and Southeast Asia, speech, Washington, D.C., June 17, 1968 (Folder 15)
  - Hatta, Mohammad
    - Indonesia's Foreign Policy, reprint, Foreign Affairs, April 1953 (Folder 16)
    - Visit of, to University of California, Berkeley, May 4, 1960 (Folder 17)
  - Higgins, Benjamin, curriculum vitae (Folder 18)
  - Hughes, John, China and Indonesia: The Romance That Failed, reprint, Current Scene (Hong Kong), Vol. VI, No. 19, November 4, 1968 (Folder 19)
  - International Cooperation Administration, Indiana University, Program to Provide Technical Assistance to the Government of Indonesia, semi-annual reports
    - 1958 (Folder 20)
    - October 1959-March 1960 (Folder 21)
  - International Press Correspondence, Vol. 8, NO. 88, December 12, 1928 (Folder 22)
  - Itagaki, Yoichi, Some Notes on the Controversy Concerning Boeke's `Dualistic' Theory, July 30, 1958 (Folder 23)
  - Jones, Garth, Statistical Reports of the Daerah Istimewa Jogjakarta, Indonesia: Comments Upon Recent Developments, 1961 (Folder 24)
  - Jones, Howard P., Address to the American Society of Newspaper Editors, Washington, D.C., April 23, 1960 (Folder 25)
  - Kartohadiprodjo, Soediman, Reflections on Community Development, speech, Berkeley, April 10, 1958 (Folder 26)
  - Kramish, Arnold, Proliferation and Policy, n.d. (Folder 27)
  - Lusaka Conference, September 1970 SEE Third Conference of NA
  - Mabuchi, Toichi, The Two Types of Kinship Rituals Among Malayo-Polynesian Peoples, August 1958 (Folder 28)
  - Malaysia and the Chinese Problem, by a special correspondent of Indian Foreign Affairs, reprint, Vol. VI, No. 4, April 1963 (Folder 29)
  - Malaysian Bulletin, No: NBI, November 1, 1963 (Folder 30)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Center for International Studies, Project on the Economic and Political Development of Indonesia
    - General (Folder 31)
    - Annual Report, 1953-54 (Folder 32)
    - Agricultural Resettlement of Javanese Farmers in the Outer Islands of Indonesia Before World War II, Joachim Hurwitz, 1955 (Folder 33)
    - Bibliography
      - General, economics (Folder 34)
      - Economics (Folder 35)
    - Budget, 1953 (Folder 36)
    - Business Taxation and Regulation of Profits Transfers in Underdeveloped Countries, Benjamin Higgins, April 7, 1954 (Folder 37)
    - Central Bank Reserves System and Indonesia's Foreign Exchange Problem, Benjamin Higgins, August 11, 1954 (Box 137., Folder 1)
    - Committees (Folder 2)
    - Content and nature of program (Folder 3)
    - The Dualistic Theory of Underdeveloped Areas, Benjamin Higgins, July 8, 1954 (Folder 4)
    - Economic Development of Underdeveloped Areas: Past and Present, Benjamin Higgins, June 11, 1954 (Folder 5)
    - Encouragement of Foreign Investment in Indonesia, Benjamin Higgins, September 14, 1954 (Folder 6)
    - Entrepreneur and elite in Indonesian development (Folder 7)
    - Financing Economic Development in Indonesia, Douglas S. Paauw, 1955 (Folder 8)
    - Foreign Aid and the Cold War, Benjamin Higgins, April 1957 (Folder 9)
    - Foreign investment problems in Indonesia (Folder 10)
    - Higgins-Paauw Study, 1954 (Folder 11)